练习 1-4：纯声音。我们把它放进语境里。使用 AH 音，重复
Exercise 1-4, pure sound. Let's put this in context. Using the AH sound, repeat the
下面这些声音。不用担心它是什么意思。只要用
following sounds. Don't worry about what it means. Just repeat the sounds in a
用低沉、自信的声音重复。倒写的小 e 读作 UH。第一组：Bah、Bloss、
deep, confident voice. That little upside-down E sounds like UH. One. Bah, Bloss,
Dis, Job. Two. Scott taught a lot. Three, Don bought a bike. At this point, you may
你现在可能会想：这到底是什么？这是无意义音节。它看起来甚至不像
be thinking, what the heck is this? It's nonsense. It doesn't even look like
英语。我真的需要知道自己在说什么，可我不知道这是什么意思。
English. I really need to know what I'm saying, and I don't know what this means.
那些只是胡言乱语，我可能听起来像个傻瓜；我想靠理解内容来获得信心。
This is gibberish, and I might just sound like a fool here. I need the confidence of
我担心自己听起来非常愚蠢。
understanding what I'm saying. I'm afraid I'll sound completely foolish. I'm not
这个练习没有信心，因为它和我以前学到的太不一样了。我
confident with this because it's so different from what I've been taught. I
只是想看看它在普通英语里是什么样子。
just want to see what it looks like in regular English.